Hubungi

Jalan pelajar imam 2 Rt 08/04, Desa Pamijen, Kecematan Sokaraja, Kabupaten Banyumas, Provinsi Jawa Tengah, 53181 +6281548962893 (Mobile) 07tav2akbar@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/mochamadsyahrul-akbar-904409225 (LinkedIn)

Keahlian Teratas

React.js
JavaScript
Front-End Development

Certifications

Front-End Web Developer Expert
Getting Started Programming With
Java

Learn SOLID Programming Principles

Getting Started Programming With C Frontend Web Development with React

Mochamad Syahrul Akbar

Computer Science Student | Front End Specialist at Sagara Technology

Purwokerto, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia

Ringkasan

I am an undergraduate student in the field of information technology. I have experience as a front end web developer, and have a strong interest in the latest technology and innovations in the field of IT. I always want to learn and develop myself to be better in my field.

Pengalaman

Sagara Technology Front End Specialist Desember 2022 - Present (2 bulan) Jakarta Pusat, Jakarta Raya, Indonesia

Ruangguru.com

5 bulan

Assistant Mentor

November 2022 - Desember 2022 (2 bulan)

MSIB Ruangguru Camp holds assistant mentors to help students who have difficulty doing assignments, the assistant mentor's daily tasks are :

- 1. helping mentors provide material to students via google meet
- 2. help complete the assignments of students who take part in the Ruangguru MSIB program

Front End Engineer (Kampus Merdeka Independent Study) Agustus 2022 - Desember 2022 (5 bulan)

- Learn Thinking Skills, Project Management Tech, Communication, and Presentation Skills
- Learn Software Engineering (SDLC, Network, Algorithm, Version Control, IDE/ Code Editor, Terminal)
- Learn HTML5, CSS3, and Tailwind CSS
- Learn Javascript (OOP, Async, Modular Function)

Indosat Ooredoo Hutchison Digital Camp Front-End Web Developer | IDCAMP 2022 Mei 2022 - Desember 2022 (8 bulan)

Learn about Frontend Web Developer from beginner to expert in Dicoding, from 60k applicants to 75 graduates.

Universitas AMIKOM Purwokerto Laboratory Assistant September 2021 - Februari 2022 (6 bulan)

Purwokerto, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia

- Assisting lecturers in the practicum implementation process.
- Participate in the development of practicum materials.
- Maintain and maintain laboratory equipment and cleanliness.

LG Electronics

Electrical Maintenance Engineer Februari 2019 - April 2019 (3 bulan)

Banyumas, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia

- Diagnose problems that exist in electronic devices
- Repair electronic equipment (TV, monitor, washing machine, etc.)
- Provide service to consumers
- keep the work environment clean

Pendidikan

Universitas Amikom Purwokerto Bachelor's degree, Computer Science · (2020 - 2024)